# **Jimmy Andersson**

Phone: (+46) 70-895 35 51

E-Mail: jimmyandersson89@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

I'm a web developer from Sweden that just finished my education at university. I've worked in IT for over 4 years before I began my studies. I have experience in server administration and IT support. During my recent time in school I've learned Javascript, PHP and Python. I've also learned to manage and build databases, MySQL, SQLite and Mongodb are the ones I've worked the most with. I like to learn new technologies.

## **EDUCATIONS**

2018 – Now Web Development (Remote) at Blekinge Technical University (BTH), the main languages used is Javascript, PHP and Python. I've learned development in both frontend and backend in all three languages.

2010 – 2013 Network and Systemadministration at Skövde University (HiS), learned to manage servers and networks, here I've managed both Windows servers and Linux servers.

#### **EXPERIENCES**

2017 – 2019 2 years	<b>Business Owner, at JimIT</b> , I helped both companies and people with their computers and networks and also made websites for my customers.
2015 – 2016 1.5 years	<b>Onsite Technician</b> , <b>at Metsä Tissue</b> , assisted users with their computer problems daily and managed servers.
2014 – 2015 1 year	<b>IT Technician</b> , <b>at Netred AB</b> , helped companies and their users, fixing computer problems, purchasing and installing them. Also managed their servers and network.
2013 – 2014 1 year	<b>Servicedesk agent, at Volvo IT</b> , assisted users via phone and email, fixing their computer problems.

### **SKILLS**

## IT

Microsoft Office, LibreOffice, Photoshop, GIMP, Windows, Linux, OSx.

## **Web Development**

Javascript, PHP, Python, Node.js, Express, Vue.js, React.js, Flask, Docker, Mongodb, MySQL, MariaDB, Wordpress, Git.

## **Data Science**

Pandas, Matplotlib, Numpy

#### **Administration**

Windows Server, Linux, Active Directory, Exchange, Vmware, Virtualbox, Network, Cisco, CCNA 1-5.

#### **HOBBIES**

I like to spend time with my fiance and our dog, watch films and series, play computer games and play golf.